<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>//172.234.245.214:80/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>service@fearlessgeekmedia.com (Fearless Geek Media)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>service@fearlessgeekmedia.com (Fearless Geek Media)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//172.234.245.214:80/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m back, program wasn&#39;t quite three months</title>
      <link>//172.234.245.214:80/post/im-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>service@fearlessgeekmedia.com (Fearless Geek Media)</author>
      <guid>//172.234.245.214:80/post/im-back/</guid>
      <description>So I found out while I was in the program that it wasn&amp;rsquo;t necessarily for three months. Besides, my insurance would only cover 45 days.&#xA;It&amp;rsquo;s all good. I got the healing I needed for the time being. Now I&amp;rsquo;m ready to get to work on some awesome projects.&#xA;Development projects I was able to do while in treatment:&#xA;A javascript CLI app for contacts, compiled with Bun A Mad Libs clone I call GeekyLibs I&amp;rsquo;m also refreshing myself on Python.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In 3 month residential treatment for mental health.</title>
      <link>//172.234.245.214:80/post/update-out-for-three-months/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>service@fearlessgeekmedia.com (Fearless Geek Media)</author>
      <guid>//172.234.245.214:80/post/update-out-for-three-months/</guid>
      <description>Hi everyone! Well, interestingly, the same day I made my last post that said I was doing better, I had a bit of a meltdown and crisis later that day.&#xA;I spent a week in the hospital, and then was recommended for residential therapy at a local treatment program. This program also has an option for transitional housing at the end. This will be great since I&amp;rsquo;m at the shelter right now, and that takes a toll on me as it is.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Had to take a mental health break...</title>
      <link>//172.234.245.214:80/post/mental-health-break/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>service@fearlessgeekmedia.com (Fearless Geek Media)</author>
      <guid>//172.234.245.214:80/post/mental-health-break/</guid>
      <description>Hi everyone! I had hoped to work on certain projects a bit more, but I pretty much needed a mental health break. I had several weeks where it was a struggle for me. So I didn&amp;rsquo;t focus on FearlessCMS or the other projects like I really wanted to.&#xA;January is generally a rough month for me anyway. Perhaps January should just be a month where I largely focus on my mental health going forward for me.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Year, New Site!</title>
      <link>//172.234.245.214:80/post/new-year-new-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>service@fearlessgeekmedia.com (Fearless Geek Media)</author>
      <guid>//172.234.245.214:80/post/new-year-new-site/</guid>
      <description>Well, it&amp;rsquo;s a new year! And a lot has changed! I have decided to redo my website. Honestly, it&amp;rsquo;s still in progress, but I wanted to go ahead and get something up as I took the old site down several months ago.&#xA;I have started my own new projects, but also looking for new clients in this new year.&#xA;I have made some changes in my life. I have moved to Salt Lake City, Utah!</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
